const quizData = [
    {
        question: 'What were Daenerys\' three dragons\' names?',
        answers: [
            'Jon, Robb, and Bran',
            'Viserys, Khal Drogo, and Khaleesi',
            'Drogon, Rhaegal, and Viserion',
            'Dracarys, Morghulis, and Dohaeris'
        ],
        displayedQuestionNumber: 1,
        correctAnswer: 'Drogon, Rhaegal, and Viserion',
        house: 'Targaryen',
        
    },
     { 
        question: 'Which Game of Thrones character takes the crown at the end of Season 8?',
        answers: [
            'Jon Snow',
            'Daenerys Targaryen',
            'Sansa Stark',
            'Bran Stark'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Bran Stark',
        house: 'Stark'
    },
    {   
        question: 'Who was blamed for Joffrey\'s death at The Purple Wedding?',
        answers: [
            'Tyrion Lannister',
            'Sansa Stark',
            'Margaery Tyrell',
            'Olenna Tyrell'

        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Tyrion Lannister',
        house: 'Lannister'
    },
    {
        question: 'Who frees Tyrion and saves him from execution for the murder of Joffrey?',
        answers: [
            'Cersei Lannister',
            'Tywin Lannister',
            'Jaime Lannister',
            'Sansa Stark'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Jaime Lannister',
        house: 'Lannister'
    },
    {  question: 'What do we say to the God of Death?',
       answers: [
           'Not Today',
           'Today',
           'Tomorrow',
           'Yesterday'
       ],
       correctAnswer: 'Not Today',
       house: 'Braavosi'
    },
    {
        question: 'Who was responsible for the death of Jon Arryn?',
        answers: [
            'Varys',
            'Peter Baelish',
            'Lysa Arryn',
            'Eddard Stark'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Peter Baelish',
        house: 'Baelish'
    },
    {
        question: 'What was Arya\'s sword\'s name?',
        answers: [
            'Littlefinger',
            'Crochet',
            'Pointy end',
            'Needle'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Needle',
        house: 'Stark'
    },
    {
        question: 'What happened to Arya\'s direwolf Nymeria?',
        answers: [
            'She went to go live in the wild',
            'She was murdered',
            'She went to live north of the Wall',
            'She stayed in Winterfell'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'She went to go live in the wild',
        house: 'Stark'
    },
    {
        question: 'Where was Margaery Tyrell from?',
        answers: [
            'King\'s Landing',
            'Winterfell',
            'Highgarden',
            'Casterly Rock'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Highgarden',
        house: 'Tyrell'
    },
    {
        question: 'What was the symbol of House Tyrell?',
        answers: [
            'A rose',
            'A daffodil',
            'A sunflower',
            'A daisy'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'A rose',
        house: 'Tyrell'

    }
        
];
